Charles A. and June R. P. Ross Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Locality Information, Series I
  - Maps., 002879
    - Map. USGS advance sheet topographic quadrangle - Helena, Mich (SW quarter). Scale 1:31680. 1932 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002890
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Bone Spring, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1920 edition, [first published in 1918], reprinted 1932. Mounted on canvas. Not annotated with localities., 003042
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - West Cincinnati, Ohio - Kentucky. 1914 edition, reprinted in 1933. Scale 1:62500. Not annotated with localities., 002745
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Mt. Lewis, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with Hoare's locality SW/SE/sec35 (circled on map)., 1935; 002975
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - East Cincinnati, Ohio - Kentucky. 1914 edition, reprinted in 1936. Scale 1:62500. Not annotated with localities., 002746
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Payson - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1936; 002812
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Mountain City, Nevada - Idaho. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with some comments on lithology and dip; annotated with localities including PN 4184p and PN 4185p., 1936; 002973
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Rowland, Nevada - Idaho. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with Hoare's fusulinid locality., 1936; 002982
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Diamond Butte - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1937; 002798
    - Map. USGS 30' topographic quadrangle - Fort Davis, Texas. Scale 1:125000. 1897 edition, reprinted 1937. Mounted on canvas. Not annotated with localities, 003044
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Klondyke - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1938; 002808
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Silver Reef Mountains - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1940; 002819
    - Map. US Geologic Survey base index map - Arizona. 1940 edition, reprinted in 1953. Not annotated with localities., 002850
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Antler Peak, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities, including PN-4126 [bottom] thru PN-4132 [top] and PN-4034-F through PN-4037-F., 1940; 002951
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Clarkdale - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1944; 002796
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Antelope Peak - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1946; 002787
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Hess Canyon, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1923 edition, reprinted 1946. One reprint and three photocopies, all annotated with pencilmarks and one of which is annotated with blue stream valleys. Not annotated with localities., 003037
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Hess Canyon, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1923 edition, reprinted 1946. Mounted on canvas. Annotated with locations of two wells which were cored/logged [including Jo Anne Moore #1 and Montgomery #1]., 003038
    - Map. USGS 30' topographic quadrangle - Alpine, Texas. Scale 1:125000. 1895 edition, reprinted 1949. Mounted on canvas. Not annotated with localities., 1946; 003039
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Monument Spring, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1921 edition, reprinted 1946. Annotated with localities [see center N edge of map area]., 003046
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Monument Spring, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1921 edition, reprinted 1946. Mounted on canvas. Annotated with King's Dugout Ck. [Loc. 8094; 1937], 003047
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Ash Fork - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1947; 002788
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Globe - Arizona. Scale 1:24000 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1947; 002804
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Paulden - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1947; 002811
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Garden Valley, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4025A-F, PN-4026-F and PN-4026B-F., 1949; 002963
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Mt. Lewis, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with localities including PN-4039-P through PN-4041-P and PN-4042-F., 1949; 002974
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Roberts Creek Mtn., Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4061-F., 1949; 002980
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Altuda, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1923 edition, reprinted 1949. Mounted on canvas. Not annotated with localities, but does contain some pencil marks [marking roads and possible position of a measured section?], 003040
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Altuda, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1923 edition, reprinted 1949. Annotated with localities [See Associations Tab]., 003041
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Marathon, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1921 edition, reprinted 1949. Mounted on canvas. Not annotated with localities., 003045
    - Map. USGS 30' topographic quadrangle - Shafter, Texas. Scale 1:125000. 1896 edition, reprinted 1949. Mounted on canvas. Not annotated with localities., 003048
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Sierra Madera, Texas. Scale 1:62500. 1923 edition, reprinted 1949. Mounted on canvas. Not annotated with localities., 003049
    - Map. Map of Canberra. Scale 60 mm: 1 mile. Printed by the Property & Survey branch of the Department of the Interior, Australia., 1950; 003210
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Santa Rita, Grant County - New Mexico. Scale 1:24000 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1951; 002785
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Cibola, Arizona - California. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1951; 002795
    - Map. Geological sketch map of the Yass District (annotated), reprinted from the Journal and Proceedings of the Royal Society of New South Wales, vol. LXXXV, 1951., 003209
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Hereford - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1952; 002806
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Carlin, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4003-F thru PN-4005-F, PN 4142 thru PN-4149; PN-4147 is broken up into four separate localities including PN-4147 A, B, C and X., 1952; 002956
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Dixie Flats, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with localities including PN-4006-F thru PN-4010-F, PN-4015-F thru PN-4022-F; contains additional pencil marks corresponding to an additional locality., 1952; 002959
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Elko East, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Various Pennsylvanian formational contacts are drawn; this map contains no annotated localities., 1953; 002961
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Pinto Summit, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with localities including PN-4067-F thru PN-4076-F., 1953; 002979
    - Map. USGS 30' topographic quadrangle - Florence - Arizona. 1900 edition, reprinted in 1955. Scale 1:125000. Not annotated with localities., 002801
    - Map. USGS 2 x 1 degree topographic map - Winnemucca, Nevada. Revised 1971 version. Scale 1:250000. Not annotated with localities, but a place named "Red Hill" is marked and circled on the map., 1955; 002993
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Ackerman Canyon, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities PN-4096-F thru PN 4099-F., 1956; 002949
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Antelope Peak, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Three copies annotated with localities, including PN-4028-F, PN-4062-OR and PN-4063-F through PN-4066-F., 1956; 002950
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Bartine Ranch, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with localities, including PN-4027-OR [60 S Sample]., 1956; 002952
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Robinson Mtn., Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4087-F, PN-4088-OR, PN-4089-F thru PN-4092-F, PN-4172-F and PN-4173-F., 1956; 002981
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Wild Horse, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with formational contacts, structures and features (e.g., turbidites) and localities including PN-4141., 1956; 002991
    - Map. USGS 2 x 1 degree topographic map - Ely, Nevada - Utah. Revised 1971 version. Scale 1:250000. Not annotated with localities, but with markings of where to find high-quality sections of the Ely Limestone., 1956; 002994
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Bellota Ranch - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1957; 002789
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Cortaro - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1957; 002797
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Rincon Valley - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1957; 002815
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Tubac - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1957; 002823
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Twin Peaks - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1957; 002824
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Winchester Mts. - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1957; 002825
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Maricopa County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1957; 002845
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Hastings, Minn. - Wis. 1957 edition. Scale: 1:62500. Not annotated with localities., 002881
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Battle Mountain, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Annotated with localities, including R-147A-OR, R-147B-OR, R-148A-OR and R-152A-OR thru R-152C-OR., 1957; 002953
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Beowawe, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4059-F and PN-4060-F., 1957; 002954
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Diamond Springs, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4077 thru PN-4085, PN-4101-F thru PN-4104-F, PN-4106-F, PN-4150-F thru PN-4157-F., 1957; 002958
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Frenchie Creek, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including G-2A through G-2C, 1-A thru 1-C and PN-4038-F., 1957; 002962
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Horse Creek Valley, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4023-F and PN-4024-F., 1957; 002966
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Horse Heaven Mtn, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4093-F and PN-4094-F., 1957; 002967
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Elgin - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002799
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Empire Mountains - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002800
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Fort Huachuca - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002802
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Gleeson - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002803
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Happy Valley - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002805
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Mount Wrightson - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002809
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Pearce - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002813
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Sahuarita - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002816
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - St. David - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002820
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Sunnyside - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002821
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Swisshelm Mtn. - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002822
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Mohave County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002842
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Yavapai County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1958; 002847
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Escanaba, Michigan: Wisconsin. Scale 1:250000. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002882
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Cooks, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002883
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Corner Lake, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002884
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Garden, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002885
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Gladstone, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002886
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Peninsula Point, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002891
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Rapid River, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002892
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Rock, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002893
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Steuben, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002894
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Trenary, Mich. Scale 1:62500. 1958 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002895
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Huntsman Ranch, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Annotated with localities including PN-4189p thru PN-4192p, 1958; 002968
    - Map. USGS Reconnaisance geologic map of southeastern Cochise County, Arizona [MF-213]. Scale 1:125000 - Datum MSL. Not annotated with localities, 1959; 002782
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Black Peak, Arizona - California. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1959; 002790
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Parker Dam, Arizona - California. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1959; 002810
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Gila County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1959; 002839
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Pinal County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1959; 002840
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Mohave County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1959; 002841
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Cochise County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1959; 002844
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Saint Paul, Minnesota. Scale 1:250000. 1959 edition. Not annotated with localities., 002880
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Jiggs, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Marked with a circle, likely indicating a collection locality. Not explicitly annotated with localities., 1959; 002969
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Kittridge Springs, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Partially mapped with formational contacts and at least one fault. Not annotated with localities., 1959; 002970
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Holbrook - Arizona. Scale 1:250000. Not annotated with localities., 1960; 002832
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Pima and Santa Cruz counties, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1960; 002843
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Coconino County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1960; 002846
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Navajo and Apache counties, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1960; 002848
    - Map. Arizona Bureau of Mines, University of Arizona - Geologic Map - Yuma County, Arizona. Scale 1:375000. Not annotated with localities., 1960; 002849
    - Map. USGS Reconnaisance geologic map of the Willcox, Fisher Hills, Cochise, and Dos Cabezas quadrangles [MF-231] - Cochise and Graham counties, Arizona. Scale 1:62500. Not annotated with localities., 1960; 002854
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Wildcat, Nevada. Scale 1:62500. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4095-F and PN-4100-F., 1960; 002990
    - Map. USGS Reconnaisance geologic map of parts of the San Pedro and Araviapa valleys, South-Central Arizona [MF-238]. Scale 1:125000 - Datum MSL. Not annotated with localities, 1961; 002783
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Cibecue - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1961; 002794
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Hope - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1961; 002807
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Salome - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1961; 002817
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Show Low - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1961; 002818
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Woods Canyon - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1961; 002826
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - Young - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1961; 002827
    - Map. USGS 7.5' Preliminary geologic quadrangle [MF-81] - Pinal Ranch - Arizona. Scale 1:24000. Not annotated with localities., 1961; 002856
    - Map. Texaco Touring Map of Wisconsin, annotated by June Ross. The map has been annotated with a line tracing her route from the southern border of Wisconsin to the border with Michigan (Upper Peninsula)., 1962; 002760
    - Map. Texaco Touring Map of Michigan, annotated by June Ross. The map has been annotated with a line tracing her route through the Upper Peninsula of Michigan., 1962; 002761
    - Map. USGS Geologic Map - Bright Angel Quadrangle - Arizona. Scale 1:48000 - Datum MSL. Not annotated with localities, 1962; 002784
    - Map. USGS 15' topographic quadrangle - San Carlos Reservoir - Arizona. Scale 1:62500 - Datum NAD27. Not annotated with localities., 1962; 002786
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Tuscon - Arizona. Scale 1:250000. Not annotated with localities., 1962; 002828
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Silver City - New Mexico. Scale 1:250000. Not annotated with localities., 1962; 002829
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Clifton, Arizona - New Mexico. Scale 1:250000. Not annotated with localities., 1962; 002834
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Ajo, Arizona, United States - Mexico. Scale 1:250000. Not annotated with localities., 1962; 002835
    - Map. Phillips 66 Touring Map of Minnesota, annotated by June Ross. The map has been annotated with a line tracing her route through southern Minnesota for July 1962, 002878
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Elko East, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Photorevised version 1975. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4013-F and PN-4014-F., 1962; 002960
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Osino, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Annotated with localities including PN-4011-F and PN-4012-F., 1962; 002976
    - Map. Texaco Touring Map of Ohio, annotated by June Ross. The map has been annotated with circles denoting collecting localities throughout southwestern Ohio., 1962; 003189
    - Map. Texaco Touring Map of Indiana, annotated by June Ross. The map has been annotated with circles denoting collecting localities in eastern Indiana., 1962; 003190
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Prescott - Arizona. Scale 1:250000. 1956 Edition (limited revision 1962). Not annotated with localities., 1963; 002830
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Nogales, Arizona, United States - Mexico. Scale 1:250000. 1956 Edition (limited revision 1962). Not annotated with localities., 1963; 002831
    - Map. Standard Oil Touring Map of Louisville and Jefferson County, Kentucky, annotated by June Ross. The map has been annotated with circles denoting collecting localities in western Kentucky., 1963; 003191
    - Map. Mobil Touring Map of Kentucky and Tennessee, annotated by June Ross. The map has been annotated with dots denoting collecting localities in western Kentucky and southern Indiana., 1963; 003192
    - Map. USGS 2x1 degree topographic quadrangle - Douglas, Arizona - New Mexico. Scale 1:250000. Not annotated with localities., 1964; 002833
    - Map. USGS 22.5' x 10' geologic map [I-418] - S Mule Mountains, Cochise County, Arizona. Scale 1:48000. Not annotated with localities., 1964; 002852
    - Map. USGS 7.5' geologic quadrangle [GQ-354] - Dough Mountain - Arizona. Scale 1:24000. Not annotated with localities., 1964; 002855
    - Map. USGS Geologic Map of the state of New Mexico - United States. Scale 1:500000. Not annotated with localities., 1965; 002872
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Golconda, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Photorevised version 1981. Three copies annotated with localities including PN-4029-F thru PN-4033-F and PN-4046-F thru PN-4058-F., 1965; 002964
    - Map. USGS 15' geologic quadrangle [GQ-544] - Chediski Peak - Arizona. Scale 1:62500. Not annotated with localities., 1966; 002853
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Morgan Hill, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Annotated with localities including PN 6064 F and PN 6064 G, PN 4165 F thru PN 4167 F., 1967; 002972
    - Map. USGS 7.5' geologic quadrangle [GQ-668] - Brandenburg Mountain - Pinal County, Arizona. Scale 1:24000. Not annotated with localities. Accompanied with map unit description (3-page insert)., 1968; 002857
    - Map. USGS 7.5' geologic quadrangle [GQ-669] - Holy Joe Peak - Pinal County, Arizona. Scale 1:24000. Not annotated with localities. Accompanied with map unit description (3-page insert)., 1968; 002858
    - Map. USGS 7.5' geologic quadrangle [GQ-670] - Lookout Mountain - Pinal County, Arizona. Scale 1:24000. Not annotated with localities. Accompanied with map unit description (2-page insert)., 1968; 002859
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Blanchard Mtn, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Annotated with a transect of Permian strata; not annotated with localities., 1968; 002955
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Holborn, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Two copies annotated with localities including PN-4107-F and PN-4108-F., 1968; 002965
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Knoll Mountain, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Annotated with the type section of the Quilichi Fm; annotated with localities including PN-4174-F through PN-4176-F., 1968; 002971
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Pequop, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Three copies annotated with localities including PN-4044-F, PN-4045-F, PN-4086-F, PN-4109-F and PN-4110-F., 1968; 002977
    - Map. USGS 7.5' topographic quadrangle - Pequop Summit, Nevada. Scale 1:24000. Annotated with localities including PN-4043-F., 1968; 002978